Shailesh Manjunath Bhat



amshaileshpayments@gmail.com

\+91-9920070452



linkedin.com/in/amshailesh

Portfolio Link: http://amshailesh.github.io

A7402 Adwait CHS, Star colony, manpada road, dombivili east, thane, Maharashtra, India - 421204

Summary

+7 years of experience in ecommerce cataloging and Fresher in PHP and Selenium Automation testing environment.

Skills:

HTML 5, CSS 3, JavaScript, Java, PHP, JQuery, My SQL, MS Excel, MS SQL, JIRA, Selenium IDE, JUnit, POM, TestNG, Cucumber, Manual Testing

Education

University of Mumbai, Model College Bachelor's degree, Information Technology 2006 – 2009

FUTURE

iFuture Technologies Private Limited Aug 2022 – Feb 2023

- Software Testing Course, Manual + Selenium,
- HTML CSS, JIRA, JUnit, Cucumber, POM, Selenium Java,
- manual testing, automation testing, C, C++, Java

seed SEED Infotech Ltd

Nov 2019 - Mar 2020 (5 months) Learnt HTML, CSS, Javascript, Jquery, PHP & MySQL

Work Experience

Self Employed

MonthlyFair

Feb 2019 - Oct 2019

- Selling electronic devices & clothes online.
- Listing on Amazon, Order Processing & Dispatch.
- 4 Months Part time Amazon, Flipkart, Myntra & Cloudtail Order Processing, Invoice submission & Dispatch & Returns management, Amazon AMS Ads Management for a client.

Group Lead

Lumina Datamatics

Jan 2018 - Oct 2018

- Working for Amazon US process, Artificial Intelligence learning based, this involved submitting exact & alternate products so as to make AI bot learn to find the most cheapest products for future Amazon US Business Customers.
- Finding Exact & alternate products.
- Comparing Exact & Alternate products.
- Entering details inhouse portal.
- · Quality check.
- · Assigning Work to team members.
- Weekly Review of performance of team members

Many Catalog Associate

Maayra Retail

Aug 2016 - Dec 2017

- Monitoring Uploads Reporting Listings status on individual websites to CEO.
- Maintaining updatedcatalog in Top 25 websites like Amazon India, UK, US, Flipkart, Snapdeal, Shopclues & Paytm,
- Limeroad etc. Coordinating with the procurement team for new products data. Uploading new
 products on marketplaces Amazon India, UK, US, Flipkart, Snapdeal, Shopclues & Paytm, Limeroad
 etc.
- Updatingprices, Inventory, images, keywords etc.

Catalog Associate

Just Buy Live Enterprise Pvt. Ltd.

Sep 2015 - Apr 2016

- Adding new products. Maintaining updated online catalog.
- Responsible for maintenance of the website, Product updates,
- Offer Update, updating prices, stocks, writing reviews, uploading banners.

Catalog Associate

Naaptol Online Shopping Pvt. Ltd Jun 2011 - Sep 2015 (4 years 4 months)

- Adding new products.
- Maintaining updated online catalog.
- Responsible for maintenance of the website, Product updates,
 Offer Update, updating prices, stocks, writing reviews, uploading banner.

My Projects:

PHP Project: https://decocoatestore.co.in/apc/indexmain.php

Static Website Projects:

- www.pliogrip.co.in | Resins & Chemicals Company
- www.ecotechpolymers.net | Eco Friendly Inks Company
- www.vedantcommodities.com | Engineering Exports Company

Languages Known:

English Hindi Marathi Kannada